Privacy & Terms

### TERMS OF USE

Google Play subscriptions : you can manage the subscriptions in one of the following ways: 1- On Android, open the Google Play Store, then tap Menu > Subscriptions. 2-On a computer, go to play.google.com, then in the left menu click My subscriptions. On either Android or a computer, use the URL http://play.google.com/store/account/subscriptions to open the user's list of subscriptions.

Real Caller is firmly committed to provide the best service for our clients taking into consideration the security and protection of the personal integrity of our users. The terms of use policy below explains the conditions of use you should follow in order to be able to use this service.

Real Caller offers users global phone directory lookup service transacted through a licensed application (the "Real Caller ") for mobile devices. The Terms of Service will govern your use of Real Caller software applications (including the Real Caller ), websites or other online services (all collectively "Services"), irrespective of release version. By accessing or using any of the Services, You agree to be bound by these Terms. Certain features of the Services may be subject to additional guidelines, terms or rules, which will be posted in or on the Services in connection with such features. All such additional terms, guidelines and rules are incorporated by reference into these Terms.

### 1.1 Installation & Registration

When you install the Real Caller service on your device, it will access some technical information about your device (such as: the unique device ID number and what operating system, operator, and version of the Real Caller app you use), in order to register your device and to be able to provide you with the appropriate content related to the service. . We collect the data about your searches within the Real Caller network, the phone numbers that called you, issues you may encounter, and the information you provide us with.

### 1.2 your use of Real Caller

1.2.1 Search Tab: The service is aimed to perform search by name. When you input search criteria, we send the search to our server and perform a search and return results only if available. When you search by name, you get multiple results for users with the name you're looking for. Searching by number will reveal to you the name linked to that number from our database of users.

1.2.2 Caller ID Tab: Instant Caller Id . The service is aimed to provide instant caller id , which means its goal is to identify the name associated with phone numbers that call you, and for this purpose we collect the phone number during call receive , to send it to our server just to perform search and get back to you with a result name if available. Additionally, you can add phone numbers to block list so we will block calls from any number within the block list.

1.2.3 Recent Tab: Once we found a result from searched you make, we add the results to the Recent tab to facilitate for you the way you locate the numbers and the associated names found by Real Caller . You can delete the Recent logs anytime from within this view.

1.2.4 Subscription Tab: Some enhanced search results are not for free, and you need to subscribe to this advanced Real Caller service.

### 2\. PRIVACY POLICY

Upon installation, the application will ask permission to access certain information on your mobile device. The privacy policy below explains how and why we collect that data, what is it used for, and where it is stored.

2.1 The application will ask your permission to:

In comply with Google Play developer policy, below is an explanation of needed permissions.

By accepting Privacy and Terms of Use conditions you allow Real Caller to:

Search feature:  
To be able to use the search feature, you need to grand the below permission:  
android.permission.READ\_PHONE\_STATE  
\- the Device ID: In order to properly provide you the search feature, we identify your device by accessing the device id and generating a  
unique id based on this device id to be your unique id with us.  
  
Block call feature:  
If you would like to use the caller ID or Block call feature, you need to grand the below permission:  
android.permission.CALL\_PHONE  
\- Caller ID: We will access calls information to perform search in our server and get the caller name  
\- Call Blocker: We will access calls information to perform block  
  
Below permission is needed to be able to keep caller id feature functional even after the mobile device is rebooted.  
android.permission.RECEIVE\_BOOT\_COMPLETED  
  
Below permission is needed to be able to keep caller id and call blocker features functional even if the app was in background for long time.  
android.permission.WAKE\_LOCK  
  
Below permission is needed to be able to display the Caller Name info on your device screen when you receive a call.  
android.permission.SYSTEM\_ALERT\_WINDOW  
  
You can enable the below permission if you would like to use voice speech to text recognition during search.  
android.permission.RECORD\_AUDIO  

2.1.1 Read phone status and identity and directly call phone numbers: For the purpose of identifying the incoming caller and have the ability to block calls from the caller phone number if block should occur based on your block list from within the app

2.1.2 Full network access, and view network connections: For the purpose of better serving you with regards to your internet connection and fix operating and technical issues if any arise. Note, that the service will not work without internet connection, it uses 3G or WIFI connection to use your search criteria, phone number or name or your Call caller, to send it to our server and perform a search.

2.1.3 Run at startup: For the purpose of starting the live caller id service and the Chat service when you turn on your device, without that you need to manually open the application again.

2.1.4 Real Caller will ask your permission to keep the phone from sleeping so that as long as you keep the app open it's always ready for your use.

2.1.5 Draw over other networks: For the purpose to display the caller name on your screen when you receive a call, while Real Caller is not currently opened. We will display a small white window with the name, phone number country and Real Caller logo.

2.1.6 Google play billing service: For the purpose of adding new features to the application that may not be available for free.

### 3\. License and Restrictions

Subject to the terms of this Agreement, Real Caller hereby grants you a limited, personal, Non-commercial, non-exclusive, non-sub-licensee, non-transferable, non-assignable, free of charge license to download, install, access and use the Real Caller Application For your personal use "ONLY" However you may use Real Caller Application within your work or profession, in accordance with the terms of this Agreement. You will not sell, assign, rent, lease, distribute, export, import, reverse engineer ,attack, harm, recompiling, disassembling, scraping or hacking ,edit ,delete ,modify ,remove, overwrite ,spider, virus, worm, Trojan-horse, time bomb or any other codes or instructions that are designed to attack, distort, delete, damage, disassemble or otherwise interfere with the Real Caller Services or network, conceal or otherwise make the UI inaccessible or violate Real Caller Services act as an intermediary or provider, or otherwise grant rights or access to third parties with regard to the Real Caller Services or any part thereof. All content you share it with Real Caller , you should have the right to share it with Real Caller and other Users. And You agree not to challenge Real Caller rights in or otherwise attempt to assert any rights in the Services may not be used in any way, which is illegal, harmful or may be considered offensive by Real Caller , other Users or third parties. You therefore agree not to exploit the Services in any unauthorized way whatsoever, including but not limited to, trespass or burdening network capacity

### Intellectual property rights

the design of Real Caller application along with Real Caller Intellectual property rights :The design of Real Caller application along with Real Caller ,content ,design and scripts ,networks, systems, Website ,Documentation or any other materials are and shall remain the exclusive and subject to copyright and other intellectual property rights, We disallow, modify, changing, copying, or distribution our services without authorization and You acknowledge do not violate, infringe, or challenge

### Open Source

all open sources shall remain licensed for authors whenever being used

### Usage of Real Caller

Real Caller Application is free of charge however some of Real Caller Services are paid Such As People Lookup ,and you are permitted to use this application for personal use "only" and You will use the Real Caller Services exclusively for lawful purposes, Real Caller reserves the right to edit, correct, take down, store and/or permanently delete any material shared by you , or other use of the Real Caller Services that Real Caller in its discretion deems to be in breach of the above rules or otherwise inappropriate for any reason, or no reason ,Real Caller have the rights to suspend or terminate any user account without prior notice .You acknowledge that the contents of any data or communication sent or received using the Real Caller Services is exclusively the responsibility of the person from whom such communication or content originated. You will be solely liable if you send or receive content .You may report an infringement of this Agreement or inappropriate content To Real Caller Team Support by sending email to Real Caller Team Support. to support@realcallerpublic.net , Real Caller WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT OR INDIRECT LOSS OR DAMAGE CAUSED BY THE TERMINATION OF THIS AGREEMENT WHETHER OR NOT Real Caller HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH LOSS

### commercial arrangement

If you are interested in doing anything else than permitted under this Agreement please do contact Real Caller Team Support

### Disclaimer & warranty

You may not use our service or the information it provides to make decisions about consumer credit, employment, insurance, tenant screening, or any other purpose , The information available on our website or in our service may not be 100% accurate, complete, or up to date, so do not use it as a substitute for your own due diligence. Real Caller does not make any representation or warranty about the accuracy of the information available through our website or about the character or integrity of the person about whom you inquire

Real Caller cannot guarantee that all time data will be without disruptions, delays or errors or any downtime, bugs or mistake into the application .You acknowledge that Real Caller will use its commercially reasonable efforts to protect the privacy and proper functioning of your Device and of your communications, but that Real Caller does not give any guarantees in this respect

Real Caller SERVICES ARE PROVIDED AS IS HEREBY EXCLUDES ALL WARRANTIES, WHETHER EXPRESS, IMPLIED OR STATUTORY, WITH RESPECT TO THE Real Caller SERVICES, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, WARRANTIES OF QUALITY, PERFORMANCE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANT ABILITY, OR FITNESS FOR USE OR ANY PARTICULAR PURPOSE OR REQUIREMENT. Real Caller DOES NOT REPRESENT OR WARRANT THAT THE Real Caller SERVICES WILL ALWAYS BE AVAILABLE, ACCESSIBLE, UNINTERRUPTED, TIMELY, SECURE, ACCURATE, COMPLETE AND ERROR-FREE OR WILL OPERATE WITHOUT MESSAGE, FILE OR PACKET LOSS, NOR DOES Real Caller WARRANT ANY CONNECTION TO OR TRANSMISSION FROM THE INTERNET OR ANY FIXED OR MOBILE COMMUNICATIONS NETWORK, OR ANY QUALITY, ACCURACY OR RELIABILITY OF COMMUNICATIONS MADE THROUGH THE Real Caller SERVICES.

### Real Caller Paid Services

Payments will be made exclusively to Real Caller and You need to agree to any specific terms presented at the moment of making a payment, including without limitation provisions relating to processing of personal data by that service provider which may differ from Real Caller policies and for which Real Caller is not responsible. You are solely responsible for any charges incurred using your User Account and direct notify Real Caller if you believe that unauthorized access occur in your Account, please note that always check the up to date charges before proceed any payments. If you encounter any problems related to payment, pricing or use of Real Caller Paid Services, please contact our Team Support

### Obligations & Indemnification

All Real Caller Users Should provide true, accurate, up to date and complete registration contact and billing information, and will at all times comply with your obligations here under as well as any and all applicable laws, regulations and policies, You agree to indemnify, defend and hold Real Caller its related company, Staff harmless from and against any and all liability and costs, including reasonable attorneys fees, in connection with or arising out of the absence, failure or outage of the Real Caller Services and/or your breach of any term of this Agreement or any applicable law or regulation, or breach of any rights of any third party, or use or misuse of the Real Caller Services, or communications made by means of the Real Caller Services. You acknowledge that the Real Caller Services may be subject to international rules that govern the export of software. You agree to comply with all applicable international and national laws that apply to the Real Caller Services as well as end-user, end-use and destination restrictions issued by national governments or international bodies .

### Limitation of Liability

YOU AGREE THAT Real Caller , ITS RELATED COMPANY AND ALL STAFF HAVE NO LIABILITY IN CONNECTION WITH OR ARISING FROM YOUR USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE THE Real Caller SERVICES PRODUCT LIABILITY OR ANY OTHER FORM OF LIABILITY, INCLUDING FOR ANY INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES(INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION ANY LOSS OF PROFIT, CONTRACT, BUSINESS, GOODWILL OR DATA, COMPUTER FAILURE OR PECUNIARY LOSS), EVEN IF Real Caller , ITS RELATED COMPANIES OR THE Real Caller STAFF YOU ALSO AGREE THAT Real Caller DOES NOT ENDORSE OR WARRANT AND ACCEPTS NO LIABILITY FOR ANY CONTACT, CORRESPONDENCE, TRANSACTIONS OR LOSS AND DAMAGE THAT MAY ARISE BETWEEN YOU AND ANY THIRD PARTY THROUGH THE Real Caller SERVICES OR Real Caller WEBSITE, WHETHER OR NOT SUCH THIRD PARTY ADVERTISES WITHIN THE Real Caller SERVICES OR Real Caller WEBSITE

### Storage and Security

we operate and may continue to operate servers in a number of jurisdictions around the world, so the server on which your Personal Information is used and stored may not be in your jurisdiction We use a variety of security technologies and procedures for the purpose of preventing loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure of Information.

### User Privacy

we value your privacy. This Privacy Policy informs you of your choices The short summary is that we do not sell, or otherwise share your personal information or data with third parties. The long form is as follows

### Information usage

we use the information we collect to operate and improve our website, apps, and customer support. to exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims, to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud or abuse, violations of our policies, or to protect our rights and property.

### Your Consent

by using our site or apps, you consent to our privacy policy, If you have questions regarding this privacy policy, you may email us.

### Changes to this policy

if we decide to change our privacy policy We will post those changes on this page and update the Privacy Policy modification date below. ,please do visit this page frequently for latest changes

### Trademarks & logos

\-iPhone is a trademark of Apple Inc registered in the U.S .

\-Android is a trademark of Google Inc.

\-Samsung is registered trademarks of Samsung Electronics Co, Ltd .

Real Caller is registered trademark of TMD INC

### Date Last Modified January 10th, 2024

© 2024 Real Caller All rights reserved
